Guide to the
Brown University Library
- Ltr to Design-Copyedit Team.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Date created: 2012-03-21 15:54:15 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-03-21 16:13:52 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Open Letter to Queer Youth Norway.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Correspondence, Blurbs, & Referrals/Date created: 2009-02-06 13:59:38 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-02-06 15:07:19 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-1 Beta 1-5.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Book 3 Chapter 1/Date created: 2010-06-28 13:06:32 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-06-29 20:02:17 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 120502 Baldi GENDER OUTLAW China(2).pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw China/Date created: 2012-07-11 11:48:40 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-11 11:49:02 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW_chapter 7_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 7 Get Ready To Do Your Gender/Date created: 2012-06-21 11:47:31 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-04 19:54:20 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Michael Shurtleff 12 Guideposts.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Workshop Handouts/Role Play Workshop/Date created: 2009-03-17 13:17:37 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-03-18 12:46:47 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- NYSAF.F TO M.Kate Bornstein (Dr. Shelton).pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/F to M Poughkeepsie/Date created: 2010-06-30 23:07:51 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-06-30 23:07:51 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- BumblingFinal JDM (2).pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/57F6CF73-8A8B-4A58-8154-FFD84FE00244/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/0/9/1/Attachments/190775/2/Date created: 2015-10-22 19:56:13 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-22 19:56:13 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Brown Reader Bornstein (KBPass 1) clean.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Itty Bitty Archive/Brown Anthology/Date created: 2013-06-09 16:35:38 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-06-09 21:43:05 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- The Same Page BC PASS.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/8/6/3/Attachments/368409/2/Date created: 2017-04-04 15:35:09 EDT-0400Date modified: 2017-04-04 15:35:09 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- TOTWK_by_KB_for_OutMag.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/TOd Trannies W Knives/Date created: 2010-04-15 15:08:03 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-04-15 15:46:04 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Face In The Mirror.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Gender Complete/Fictionmania Downloads/Date created: 2010-11-26 21:05:20 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-11-26 21:10:42 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- some text for 13-14 cat.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Newsletters/2013-2014 Catalogue/Date created: 2013-02-01 12:52:00 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-02-01 12:52:00 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- kb contacts for tony o.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/~Memoir PR/Village Voice Article/Date created: 2012-03-16 18:59:24 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-03-16 20:15:18 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-2 Borderline, Beta 1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/3-2 Borderline ƒ/Date created: 2010-09-17 14:41:39 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-01-02 09:19:05 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- gotngdraft 4-Feb-2010.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw Next Gen/Date created: 2010-02-05 14:41:36 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-02-05 14:41:38 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- ePub Best Practices for Pages.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Nerd Grrl Tech Info Folder/Date created: 2010-08-27 12:46:57 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-27 12:46:57 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Queer and Pleasant Part 3 Redux.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Book Three/Date created: 2011-08-29 17:58:50 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-29 17:59:28 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- TWEETS_only_kb_1st_sort.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Date created: 2012-05-22 15:47:42 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-22 15:49:22 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- kb_medical_history_2010 copy.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/Date created: 2013-02-13 21:18:52 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-02-13 21:31:23 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Aiden Fyre LOR HRSA-NSP.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Correspondence, Blurbs, & Referrals/aiden /Date created: 2012-05-04 23:32:04 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-04 23:32:50 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- *GSMS Foreword by BC.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail Downloads/Date created: 2011-12-22 21:01:02 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-12-22 21:22:22 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Take Back the City Talk.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/Yetta Kurland Testimonial/Date created: 2009-01-13 19:50:49 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-01-14 14:15:01 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB_Ltr_John_Emigh.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Correspondence, Blurbs, & Referrals/Date created: 2009-01-29 13:50:29 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-01-31 20:49:56 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- EINecessary Review KB Better BC 2nd pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail Downloads/Date created: 2012-02-29 16:26:42 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-02-29 16:37:44 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- The Monologues.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/theatrical pieces/Date created: 2010-08-10 16:04:28 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-10 16:04:28 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Blurb Letter Jeffrey Eugenides.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/~Memoir PR/Blurber Letters/Date created: 2011-09-27 17:19:04 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-28 13:15:05 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 9 KB Edit Chap 9.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/My New Gender Workbook - 1st Proofs for KB/Date created: 2013-01-18 09:49:11 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-18 13:33:40 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Letter to NY State re Installment.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate Bornstein Financial/Older Finances/New York State Taxes/Date created: 2011-02-21 18:29:36 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-02-21 19:33:21 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Lock the DAMN door.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/New York Living/Date created: 2011-08-28 00:11:00 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-28 00:14:27 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- CreatingChange2016.kb.workshop.proposal.pages09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Random Writings That Relate/Creating Change Workshop/creating change workshop attic/Date created: 2015-09-17 13:47:48 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-09-17 13:47:48 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB_Amherst_Details.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Attic Gigs/Amherst Spring 2010/Date created: 2010-03-29 11:52:32 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-03-29 11:52:32 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-5 Girl, After Hard Copy Edit Beta 2.0.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Book 3, Chap 5 Everybody Else's Girl/Date created: 2011-07-10 16:07:56 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-07-11 00:05:03 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- kb meds sheet 09-2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/kb-health to 2012/Date created: 2009-06-07 16:02:24 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-06-07 17:00:41 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Man Without a Family Reader.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/autobio pieces/Date created: 2010-12-03 08:27:25 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-12-03 08:48:50 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Website Marker Page.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Website at Routledge/Date created: 2013-01-27 14:07:09 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-27 14:10:13 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-4 where it gets complicated 1st merge.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/3-4 OK This Is Where It Gets Complicated/3-4 Round One/Date created: 2011-05-30 15:47:57 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-31 21:51:58 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Backup of Talking Points Post-Trans March.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Pride/Toronto Trans Pride 2011/Date created: 2011-07-01 12:46:36 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-07-01 12:46:36 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 3 Gold sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 3 Let X = X/Date created: 2012-07-01 20:47:55 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-05 19:45:54 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- kb meds sheet 09-2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/Date created: 2009-06-07 16:02:24 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-06-07 17:00:41 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Book 2 Chapter 5 - 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Book 2 Chap 5/Date created: 2009-12-12 13:51:15 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-12-29 10:43:42 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- QueerAndPleasantLaunchProgram.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Dixon Place Launch/dixon place artwork/Date created: 2012-04-29 19:46:51 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-30 11:19:16 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- gotngdraft 3-Mar-2010.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw Next Gen/Date created: 2010-03-05 10:24:29 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-03-07 22:33:45 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Dangerous Dreams Damned Desires SASSE 2010.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Date created: 2010-11-10 11:20:12 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-11-10 15:38:49 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 2 Gold sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 2 Where Is Gender?/Date created: 2012-07-01 19:23:23 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-01 19:24:47 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MWRU Director Script La Mama 2017.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Performance Scripts/MWROU La Mama 2017/Date created: 2017-04-17 20:09:11 EDT-0400Date modified: 2017-04-17 20:09:11 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 3 Sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 3 Let X = X/Date created: 2012-06-30 00:32:23 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-06-30 00:33:38 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- queer and pleasant danger book 2 KB pass 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Attic/Date created: 2011-08-05 16:08:56 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-06 14:24:12 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW chapter 7 sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 7 Get Ready To Do Your Gender/Date created: 2012-06-30 05:02:27 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-06-30 05:03:40 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Chapter 3 Ebook.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Storage/next/Hard Candy ƒ/activating candy/Hard Candy: da book/Date created: 2010-09-09 18:10:42 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-09-09 20:20:05 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Femme Conf 2010 Keynote Reader.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Femme Conf Keynote/Date created: 2010-08-15 13:37:11 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-18 15:03:29 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 8 KB Edit Chap 8 copy.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/My New Gender Workbook - 1st Proofs for KB/Date created: 2013-01-17 16:39:29 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-17 18:20:01 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Book 2 Chap 4 Family Man.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/ Book 2, Chapter 4/Date created: 2009-09-02 13:15:32 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-09-17 17:43:55 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Pet Meds Template 2016.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/1/0/3/Attachments/301998/1/Date created: 2016-11-08 13:54:23 EST-0500Date modified: 2016-11-08 13:54:23 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-5 Everybody Else's Girl Beta 1.0.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Book 3, Chap 5 Everybody Else's Girl/Date created: 2011-07-08 23:30:53 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-07-08 23:35:28 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 2 KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 2 Where Is Gender?/Date created: 2012-05-23 16:15:59 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-01 19:23:13 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Talk at Vigil Against Hate Crimes Xavier 09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Tao of Sabbath Mitvah Boddhisatva ƒ/Date created: 2009-03-30 15:34:49 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-03-31 21:21:27 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Talk to KC L&G re Brandon Teena May 14 1995.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Gender Complete/Date created: 2011-05-17 23:54:36 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-17 23:54:37 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB_Endorses_Yetta_Kurland.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Correspondence, Blurbs, & Referrals/Date created: 2009-09-08 17:47:51 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-09-08 19:33:14 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Barbara Carrellas One Sheet Edit.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Barbara C One Sheet/Date created: 2009-09-09 11:35:25 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-09-09 11:36:04 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Chelsea Manning Open Letter To-2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Chelsea Manning Open Letter/Date created: 2013-08-24 23:02:29 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-08-24 23:15:41 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Power of Femme Marist Conf Keynote.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Marist Women & Society Conference/Date created: 2013-08-23 16:59:31 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-08-23 16:59:31 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Queer and Pleasant Book 3, 2.0.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Book Three/Date created: 2011-08-23 19:12:14 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-23 19:17:00 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Carroll University NCOD 2010.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/8/8/1/Attachments/188987/1/Date created: 2016-11-08 16:08:16 EST-0500Date modified: 2016-11-08 16:08:16 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 6 MNGW_chapter 6_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Final Draft KB->Routledge/Chapters—Apple Pages/Date created: 2012-06-20 12:38:18 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-15 11:06:18 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Questions_for_Switzerland.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/57F6CF73-8A8B-4A58-8154-FFD84FE00244/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/0/9/1/Attachments/190948/1/Date created: 2015-10-22 19:56:14 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-22 19:56:14 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW_chapter 8_KB Pass copy.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 8 Do Your Gender Mindfully/Date created: 2012-05-29 13:04:36 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-29 17:44:45 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- queer and pleasant danger book 2 KB pass 2 cleanstart.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Attic/Date created: 2011-08-06 17:07:25 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-07 15:21:13 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Chelsea Manning Open Letter To-3.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Chelsea Manning Open Letter/Date created: 2013-08-25 14:12:03 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-08-25 14:32:54 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Aiden Fyre LOR NHSC.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Correspondence, Blurbs, & Referrals/aiden /Date created: 2012-05-04 23:33:24 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-04 23:35:37 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- HOSPITALIZATIONS--SURGERIES .pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/Block Center/Date created: 2013-03-03 17:44:44 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-03-03 17:44:44 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 10.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 10/Date created: 2012-06-27 13:55:50 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-05 19:15:10 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- An addendum to house sit.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/House Sitting/Date created: 2010-10-14 16:04:06 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-10-15 18:17:20 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Questionnaire UTPTP London 2015.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/5/6/2/Attachments/265020/2.2/Date created: 2015-10-16 11:04:42 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-16 11:04:42 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-2 Borderline.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/~~ First Draft ~~/Date created: 2011-01-06 15:31:03 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-03-19 13:02:57 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- WNE_KateB_itinerary.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/WNE Anti-Bully Conf/Date created: 2012-10-01 09:38:24 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-10-01 09:38:24 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- IRS Payment Letter Dec 2011.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate Bornstein Financial/Older Finances/IRS Payment Agreement/Monthly Payments to IRS/Date created: 2011-12-08 21:52:16 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-12-08 21:53:18 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- IRS Payment Letter Sep 2013.pages